A Guide to the Photographs of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1989-1993
Library of Virginia
- 91-0895, Gov. Wilder accepts payment of taxes from the Pamunkey and Mattaponi Indian tribes, 11/26/1991 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- 91-0896, Gov. Wilder accepts payment of taxes from the Pamunkey and Mattaponi Indian tribes, 11/26/1991 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- 91-0897, Gov. Wilder meets with Ambassadors from several African Nations, 11/26/1991 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- 91-0898, Gov. Wilder is presented a Christmas Tree for the Executive Mansion from the Tree Growers Association, 12/3/1991 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- 91-1801, Col. Lonnie Craig, Chief of Police, Division of Capitol Police, 12/9/1991 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- 91-1802, Christmas Decorations at the Gov.'s Executive Mansion, 12/9-10/1991 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- 91-1803, Christmas Decorations at the Gov.'s Executive Mansion, 12/9-10/1991 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- 91-1804, Christmas Decorations at the Gov.'s Executive Mansion, 12/9-10/1991 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- 91-1805, Christmas Decorations at the Gov.'s Executive Mansion, 12/9-10/1991 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- 91-1806, Gov. Wilder opens the exhibit about the Virginia Bill of Rights, 12/11/1991 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- 91-1807, Gov. Wilder opens the exhibit about the Virginia Bill of Rights, 12/11/1991 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- 91-1808, Gov. Wilder opens the exhibit about the Virginia Bill of Rights, 12/11/1991 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- 91-1809, Gov. Wilder opens the exhibit about the Virginia Bill of Rights, 12/11/1991 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- 91-1810, Gov. Wilder opens the exhibit about the Virginia Bill of Rights, 12/11/1991 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- 91-1811, Gov. Wilder opens the exhibit about the Virginia Bill of Rights, 12/11/1991 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- 91-1812, Gov. Wilder greets the people at the open house at the Executive Mansion, 12/12/1991 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- 91-1814, Gov. Wilder greets the people at the open house at the Executive Mansion, 12/12/1991 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- 91-1815, Gov. Wilder greets the people at the open house at the Executive Mansion, 12/12/1991 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- 91-1816, Christmas decoration on the 2nd floor of the mansion and group performing at open house at the Executive Mansion, 12/13/1991 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- 91-1818, Secretary James Dyke presented awards to several high schools for after prom and graduation parties that they held, 12/16/1991 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- 91-1819, Secretary James Dyke presented awards to several high schools for after prom and graduation parties that they held, 12/16/1991 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- 91-1821, Gov. Wilder donates a few blankets to the Holiday Blanket Campaign, 12/17/1991 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- 91-1823, Mrs. Diane Copeland, Director of the Virginia Liaison Office, 12/16/1991 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- 91-1824, State Capital in the winter months with the flags on the top, 12/16/1991 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- 91-1825, Member of EPU, Michael Darlin, 12/16/1991 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- 92122, I-295 Dedication, 259 and 36 Intersection, 6/3/1991 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- 92137, Building dedication, 7/20/1992 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- 92147, Dr. E. O. Nwado Governor of Enngu, Nigeria and Delegation, 7/27/1991 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- 92155, Introduction of State Police Superintendent Baker, 8/11/1992 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- 92160, HRD, 8/14/1991 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- 92161, Live Show: Cooke Stadium, 8/14/1992 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- 92-1826, Gov. Wilder works the State of the Commonwealth Address, 1/7/1992 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- 92-1829, Mr. J. Sergeant and family visits with Gov. Wilder prior to the State of Commonwealth Address, 1/7/1992 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- 92-1830, Gov. Wilder makes the State of Commonwealth Address to the Joint Assembly, 1/8/1992 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- 92-1831, Gov. Wilder checks house Chamber equipment for the State of Commonwealth Address, 1/8/1992 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- 92-1832, Gov. Wilder makes the State of Commonwealth Address to the Joint Assembly, 1/8/1992 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- 92-1833, Gov. Wilder addresses 6th grade students attending Richmond model violence and substance abuse prevention program, 1/14/1992 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- 92-1834, Gov. Wilder addresses 6th grade students attending Richmond model violence and substance abuse prevention program, 1/14/1992 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- 92-1835, Members of the American Legion presents a coin from the Korean war to Gov. Wilder, 1/14/1992 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- 92-1836, Gov. Wilder meets with the EEOC Commission members, 1/15/1992 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- 92-1837, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for financial aid awareness, 1/15/1992 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- 92-1838, Gov. Wilder signs a Proclamation for religious freedom day, 1/16/1992 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- 92-1839, Gov. Wilder meets Gabonese Ambassador Alex Samat and Delegation, 1/16/1992 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- 92-1840, Gov. Wilder meets Gabonese Ambassador Alex Samat and Delegation, 1/16/1992 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- 92-1841, Delegate Thomas Jackson, Jr. and family pay a courtesy call on Gov. Wilder, 1/16/1992 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- 92-1842, Gov. Wilder makes a presentation of the Victory Award certificate to the Duke family, 1/16/1992 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- 92-1843, Gov. Wilder holds a press conference to talk about the medical legislation, 1/21/1992 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- 92-1844, Members of the Baltimore Orioles pay a courtesy call to Gov. Wilder, 1/21/1992 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- 92-1845, Ms. Connie Finney and friends visits with Gov. Wilder (Box 18, Folder 5)
- 92-1846, Gov. Wilder visits with 1st lady of Colorado Mrs. Ray Bomer (Box 18, Folder 6)
- 92-1847, Gov. Wilder visits with Mr. Hough who made a courtesy call, 1/29/1992 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- 92-1848, Gov. Wilder samples the winnings of the wager with Gov. Mario Cuomo of New York from the Redskins win the Superbowl, 1/29/1992 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- 92-1849, Gov. Wilder signs a proclamation for American Heart Month, 1/31/1992 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- 92-1850, Gov. Wilder appears at the rally on his Health Care Initiative, 1/30/1992 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- 92-1852, Gov. Wilder visits with Sir Paul Reeves U.N. New Zealand and Mr. Saul Viewer, 1/31/1992 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- 92-1853, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Vocational Education Week, 2/5/1992 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- 92-1855, Gov. Wilder visit with Gen. Holomise from Transkei South Africa while paying a courtesy call, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
- 92-1856, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for National Children's Dental Health Month, 2/6/1992 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- 92-1857, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for Engineer Week, 2/6/1992 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- 92-1858, Gov. Wilder signs a Certificate of Recognition for National Agriculture Day and Virginia Agriculture Week, 2/6/1992 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- 92-1859, Gov. Wilder signs Certificate of Recognition for School Board Appreciation Week, 2/6/1992 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- 92-1860, Gov. Wilder holds a working luncheon at the Executive mansion for the Congressional Delegation, 2/7/1992 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- 92-1861, Gov. Wilder holds a working luncheon at the Executive mansion for the Congressional Delegation, 2/7/1992 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- 92-1862, Gov. Wilder holds a working luncheon at the Executive mansion for the Congressional Delegation, 2/7/1992 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- 92-1863, Gov. Wilder addresses kick-off for the students at John Kennedy High School about Drug Awareness, 2/10/1992 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- 92-1864, Gov. Wilder addresses kick-off for the students at John Kennedy High School about Drug Awareness, 2/10/1992 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- 92-1866, Gov. Wilder has lunch with the Lambert Family at the Executive Mansion, 2/10/1992 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- 92-1867, Gov. Wilder has lunch with the Lambert Family at the Executive Mansion, 2/10/1992 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- 92-1869, Gov. Wilder visits with Dr. and Mrs Richard Cheng, 2/10/1992 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- 92-1870, Gov. Wilder visits with YMCA Youth Gov. Scott Habeeb and Family, 2/18/1992 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- 92-3159, Attorney General Mary Sue Terry visits with YMCA Youth Attorney General and his family, 2/24/1992 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- 92-3160, Lt. Gov. Donald Beyers visits with YMCA Youth Lt. Gov. and her family, 2/24/1992 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- 92-9221, D.G.S. and D.F.S (Box 18, Folder 29)
- 92-9241, Conference Room: Ambassador Hong-Choo Hyun Korea, 3/18/1992 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- 92-9245, Conference room: Secretaries Week, 3/18/1992 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- 92-9246, Press Conference, 3/19/1992 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- 92-9248, Conference Room: Ambassador Mustafa Aksin Turkey, 3/20/1992 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- 93270, Wilder looks over House chamber before state address, 1/13/1993 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- 93297, Virginia Power Reception, 2/4/1993 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- 93308, Prince Charles visit to William & Mary Charter Day Ceremony, 2/13/1993 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- 93316, Konica Quality Photo, 2/17/1993 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- 93348, Bill Signing - Mansion Garden, 3/23/1993 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- 93355, Bill Cosby Executive Mansion, 3/28/1993 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- 93373, Bill signing Senators Goode and Waddell and Delegates Grayson and Armand, 4/7/1993 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- 93428, WVIR channel 29 electronic town meeting, 5/10/1993 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- 93453, Wilder on F-16 flight, National Guard at Richmond airport, 6/8/1993 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- 93494, Photo shoot Albemarle Magazine, Mansion garden, 7/22/1993 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- 93557-93573, Senegal, Wilder trip to Senegal, Uganda, Tanzania, Botswana, Mozambique, Angola, Niger, Zambia, Kenya, Cameroon, Gambia, 9/18/1993-9/19/1993 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- 93715, Mansion Open House, 12/7/1993 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous, NY Times photos, early Wilder, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous, Gov. Wilder head shots, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)